Guide to the Tamiment Library Newspapers PERIODICALS.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- V
  - Vietnam G.I. Place of publication: Chicago, Ill., 1968-1970 (Box 165)
  - Vietnam News and Reports Place of publication: Montreal, Canada, 1972-1973 (Box 466)
  - Vietnam Summer News Place of publication: Cambridge, Mass. Publisher: Vietnam Summer, 1967 (Box 465)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War/Winter Soldier Organization: [Newsletter] Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: VVAW/WSO National Prison Project, 1974 (Box 165)
  - View from the Bottom, A Place of publication: New Haven, Conn., 1969-1970 (Box 466)
  - Virginia Weekly Place of publication: Va., 1971 (Box 466)
  - Voice Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: Local 9415, Communications Workers of America, 1976 (Box 115C)
  - Voice Place of publication: Wooster, Ohio Publisher: Wooster College, 1970 (Box 466)
  - Voice Literary Supplement: VLS Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Village Voice, 1985 (Box 466)
  - Voice of 1707 / Community & Social Agency Employees Union, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Community & Social Agency Employees Union, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, 1966-1977 (Box 467)
  - Voice of 1707 / Community and Social Agency Employees Union, District Council 1707 Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Community and Social Agency Employees Union, District Council 1707, 1978-1986 (Box 467-467A)
  - Voice of Painters District Council 8 Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Painters, Tapers, and Paperhangers of Northern California, 1989-1991 (Box 468)
  - The Voice of Prisons Place of publication: Wash. Publisher: Washington State Penitentiary, 1972 (Box 342)
  - Voice of Revolution Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: U.S. Marxist-Leninist Organization, 1986-1988 (Box 467A)
  - Voice of United Painters / Published by United Painters and Paperhangers of Greater New York Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Painters and Paperhangers Union, 1963-1966 (Box 467A)
  - Voices for New Justice Place of publication: U.S.A., 1975-1976 (Box 342)
  - La Voie communiste Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: René-Boulanger, 1962 (Box 466)
  - La Voie de la paix Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: L'Union Pacifiste de France, 1962 (Box 467A)
  - Völkischer Beobachter Place of publication: Berlin, Germany Publisher: F. Eher Nachf., 1933 (Box 467A)
  - Vortex Place of publication: Lawrence, Kan., 1970-1971 (Box 467)
  - Vortex Place of publication: Lawrence, Kan., 1970-1971 (Box 467)
  - Vorwärts, Berliner Volksblatt Place of publication: Berlin, Germany Publisher: M. Bading, 1932-1933 (Box 466)
  - La Voz de la Alianza Place of publication: Albuquerque, N.M. Publisher: Alianza Federal de Pueblos Libres, 1970 (Box 97)
  - La Voz del trabajo Place of publication: San Juan, Puerto Rico Publisher: Las Organizaciones de Puerto Rico Afilidades al C.I.O., 1951 (Box 467)
  - Voz fronteriza Place of publication: San Diego, Calif., 1976-1977 (Box 467A)
  - Voz leninista Place of publication: Barcelona, Spain Publisher: Sección Bolchevique-Leninista de España (por la IV Internacional), 1937 (Box 468)
  - Voz proletaria Place of publication: Habana, Cuba Publisher: Partido Obrero Revolucionario, 1961 (Box 436)
  - Vrijbrief Place of publication: Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1983 (Box 466)
- W
  - The Wage Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Transport Workers Union, 1948 (Box 412)
  - Walrus Place of publication: Champaign, Ill., 1970-1971 (Box 467)
  - War Behind Walls Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Red Family, People Press (Box 467)
  - War Bulletin Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif., 1972-1973 (Box 468)
  - War Bulletin Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: Communist Party of Massachusetts, 1939-1940 (Box 468)
  - War Times Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: War Times, 2002-2006 (Box 468)
  - Washington, D.C. Teacher Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Teachers Union, Local 6, AFT, AFL-CIO, 1967 (Box 469)
  - Washington Free Press Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Washington Free Press Association, 1968 (Box 468)
  - Washington Observer Place of publication: Washington, D.C., 1974 (Box 468)
  - Washington Park Spirit Place of publication: Albany, N.Y. Publisher: Washington Park Spirit, Inc., 1972-1975 (Box 468)
  - Washington Peace Letter Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Washington Peace Center, 2001-2002 (Box 468)
  - Washington Teacher Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Washington, D.C., Teachers' Union, Local 6, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box 469)
  - Wassaja Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: American Indian Historical Society, 1973-1979 (Box 469)
  - Wassaja Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: American Indian Historical Society, 1982-1983 (Box 469)
  - Wassaja, the Indian Historian Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: American Indian Historical Society, 1980 (Box 469)
  - Waste Paper Place of publication: Buffalo, N.Y. Publisher: Sierra Club Nuclear Waste Campaign, 1979 (Box 469)
  - The Water Tunnel Place of publication: U.S.A., 1971 (Box 470)
  - Waves Place of publication: Seattle, Wash. Publisher: Northwest Passage, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 467)
  - WDL News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Workers Defense League, 1969 (Box 467)
  - Weather Report Place of publication: San Marcos, Tex., 1971 (Box 470)
  - Weekly News Service Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: American Federation of Labor, 1942 (Box 470)
  - Weekly People Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Socialist Labor Party, 1937, 1972-1973 (Box 470, Box 512)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7349)
  - Welfare Fighter Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Poverty-Rights Action Center, 1970-1972 (Box 470)
  - Welfare Reporter Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Public Workers, 1947-1952 (Box 470)
  - Welfare Spotlight Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Local 371, SCME, AFL-CIO, 1958 (Box 470)
  - West Bronx on the Move Place of publication: Bronx, N.Y., 1973 (Box 470)
  - West Side Torch Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: West Side Organization, 1968 (Box 470)
  - Western Voice Place of publication: Vancouver, Canada Publisher: Western Voice Collective, 1973-1976 (Box 472)
  - Western Worker Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: Communist Labor Party, 1974-1975 (Box 473)
  - What She Wants Place of publication: Cleveland, Ohio Publisher: Cleveland Women's Counsel, 1973-1979 (Box 475)
  - What the Hack Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1964 (Box 279)
  - WhatNOW Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Organization for Women, New York City Chapter, 2000-2005 (Box 310)
  - What's Happening? Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: The Lower East Side News, 1966 (Box 473)
  - Where It's At Place of publication: West Berlin, Germany Publisher: Students for a Democratic Society in West Berlin, 1967-1968 (Box 165)
  - Whig Place of publication: Angeles City, Philippines, 1971 (Box 165)
  - White Collar Place of publication: Washignton, D.C. Publisher: Office Workers International Union, 2002 (Box 473)
  - White Lightning Place of publication: Bronx, N.Y. Publisher: White Lightning Section of the Spirit of Logos, 1971-1975 (Box 473)
  - Wild Raspberry Place of publication: Hartford, Conn. Publisher: Wild Raspberry, 1971 (Box 473)
  - Wildcat Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Military Action Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 165)
  - Wildcat Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Wildcat Press, 1969-1970 (Box 473)
  - Wildcat Place of publication: San Diego, Calif., 1972-1975 (Box 473)
  - Wildcat Report Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1969-1970 (Box 473)
  - Willamette Alliance, The Place of publication: Portland, Or. Publisher: Oregon Coalition of Alternative Human Services, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Willamette Bridge Place of publication: Portland, Or. Publisher: Bridgeworks, Inc., 1968-1971 (Box 474)
  - Winter Soldier: A Publication of Vietnam Veterans Against the War Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: National VVAW Collective, 1973-1975 (Box 466)
  - WiReport Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Wire Service Guild Local 222, American Newspaper Guild of New York, 1959-1989 (Box 475)
  - Wisconsin Commonwealth Place of publication: Madison, Wis. Publisher: Labor-Farm Party, 1985-1987 (Box 473)
  - Wisconsin Patriot Place of publication: Madison, Wis. Publisher: Wisconsin Alliance, 1971-1976 (Box 475)
  - WomaNews Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Women's Focus/Womanews, 1985-1990 (Box 476)
  - Woman's World Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1971-1972 (Box 476)
  - Women and Revolution Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: The Socialist Workshop, 1971-1972 (Box 488)
  - Women United Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Women United for Action, 1973-1977 (Box 476)
  - Women's Collective Press Place of publication: Montreal, Canada Publisher: McGill University Arts and Science Undergraduate Society, 1975 (Box 476)
  - Women's Newspaper Place of publication: London?, England, 1971 (Box 477)
  - Women's Page Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif., 1970-1971 (Box 477)
  - Women's Press Place of publication: Eugene, Or., 1971 (Box 477)
  - Women's Street Theater Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: People's Press, nd (Box 477)
  - Women's Way Place of publication: Austin, Tex. Publisher: Plain View Press, 1992 (Box 476)
  - Woodhull & Claflin's Weekly Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Victoria C. Woodhull & Tennie C. Claflin, 1873 (Box 476)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7793)
  - Woodstock International: International, National, and Community News - From a Left Perspective Place of publication: Woodstock, N.Y. Publisher: Scoop Progressive Media, LLC, 2009-2011 (Box 473)
  - The Woodworker Place of publication: Gladstone, Or. Publisher: IWA-U.S., AFL-CIO, 1987-1993 (Box 204)
  - Word Place of publication: Baltimore, Md. Publisher: Communications Workers of America, Local 2101, 1985 (Box 115C)
  - The Work Force Place of publication: Albany, N.Y. Publisher: Civil Service Employees Association, 2006-current (Box 477A)
  - The Worker, 1979? (Box 371)
  - The Worker Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Workers Party, U.S.A., 2001-2002 (Box 478)
  - The Worker Place of publication: Montclair, Calif. Publisher: Labor Party League, 1975-1976 (Box 478)
  - The Worker Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Long View Publishing Company, 1968 (Box 478)
  - Worker & Soldier Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1970-1971 (Box 487)
  - The Worker for Detroit and Southeast Michigan Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Revolutionary Communist Party, USA, 1976-1977 (Box 478)
  - The Worker for Hawaii Place of publication: Honolulu, Hawaii Publisher: Revolutionary Communist Party, USA, 1975-1977 (Box 478)
  - The Worker for the Bay Area Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: Revolutionary Communist Party, USA, 1975-1978 (Box 482)
  - The Worker for the Bay Area and Salinas Valley Place of publication: Oakland, Calif. Publisher: Revolutionary Communist Party, USA, 1978-1979 (Box 482)
  - The Worker for the Milwaukee Area and Wisconsin Place of publication: Milwaukee, Wis. Publisher: Revolutionary Communist Party, USA, 1975-1978 (Box 478)
  - The Worker for the New York-New Jersey Area Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1973 (Box 470)
  - The Worker for the Northwest Place of publication: Portland, Or. Publisher: Revolutionary Communist Party, USA, 1975-1978 (Box 479)
  - Workers Action Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Workers Action Movement, 1974 (Box 479)
  - Workers' Action Place of publication: Emeryville, N.Y. Publisher: Committee for a Labor Party, 1968-1971 (Box 479)
  - Workers Action: Bulletin of the Workers Action Movement Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1974 (Box 479)
  - The Workers' Advocate Place of publication: Cleveland, Ohio Publisher: American Communist Workers Movement, 1969-1970 (Box 238)
  - Workers' Advocate: Voice of the Marxist-Leninist Party of the USA Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Marxist-Leninist Publications, 1977-1993 (Box 479-481)
  - Workers Democracy = Democracia Obrera Place of publication: Trenton, N.J. Publisher: Workers Democracy Network, 2001 (Box 478)
  - Workers News Place of publication: Sydney?, Australia Publisher: Socialist Labor League, 1980 (Box 478)
  - Workers' Power Place of publication: Highland Park, Mich. Publisher: International Socialist Publishing Company, 1971-1976 (Box 501)
  - Workers Power Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Workers Power Group, 1982 (Box 478)
  - Workers Press Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Socialist Labor League, 1970-1974 (Box 483-486)
  - Workers Struggle Place of publication: Detroit, Mich., 1981-1983 (Box 491)
  - Workers' Truth Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Revolutionary Workers Group, 1973-1975 (Box 491)
  - Workers' Unity Place of publication: London Publisher: LinkLondon: South African Congress of Trade Unions, 1978 (Box 491)
  - Workers Vanguard Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Spartacist Pub. Co., 2001-current (Box 455-455B)
  - The Workers Vanguard Place of publication: Toronto, Canada, 1962-1972 (Box 436)
  - Workers Viewpoint Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Communist Workers Party, 1976-1984 (Box 494-496)
  - Workers Voice Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Revolutionary Workers Headquarters, 1978-1980 (Box 491)
  - Workers World WW Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: WW Publishers, 1971-current (Box 491-493E)
  - Working Class Opposition: Monthly Newspaper of the Internationalist Workers Party (Fourth International) Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Internationalist Workers Party (Fourth International), 1982-1990 (Box 502)
  - Working People's Advocate Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Central Committee of the Communist League, 2005 (Box 502)
  - Working People's News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: WPN, 1988-1997 (Box 503)
  - Working People's Voice Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Graphic Communications International Union, 2005 (Box 503)
  - The Working Press Place of publication: Ithaca, N.Y. Publisher: Tompkins-Cortland Labor Coalition, 1987-1993 (Box 478)
  - The Working Teamster Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New Jersey-New York Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1992-1993 (Box 501)
  - Workmen's Circle Call Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Executive Board of Workmen's Circle, 1979-1989 (Box 501)
  - World for Peace and Democracy Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Executive Committee of the American League for Peace and Democracy, 1939 (Box 138)
  - World Revolution Place of publication: London, England Publisher: World Revolution, 1981-1993 (Box 505)
  - World War III Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: A.E. Melton, 1969 (Box 503)
  - WREE-View of Women for Racial and Economic Equality Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: WREE, 1983-1989 (Box 506)
  - WREE-View: Bulletin of Women for Racial and Economic Equality Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: WREE, 1977-1981 (Box 506)
  - Writing Place of publication: Vancouver, Canada Publisher: Georgia Straight Pub., 1970 (Box 506)
- XYZ
  - Y.C.L. News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Council, Young Communist League, 1941-1942 (Box 513)
  - Yellow Journal Place of publication: Vancouver, Canada Publisher: Pressgang Publishers, 1970 (Box 506)
  - Yipster Times Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Youth International Party News Service, 1974-1978 (Box 506)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7366)
  - El Young Lord Place of publication: Milwaukee, Wis. Publisher: The Young Lords, 1971 (Box 223)
  - Young Progressive Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Young Progressives of America, 1984 (Box 499)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7484)
  - Young Red Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Youth in Action, 1976 (Box 499)
  - Young Socialist Place of publication: London, England (Box 436)
  - Young Socialist Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Young Socialists, 1973-1981 (Box 497)
  - Young Spartacus Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Spartacus Youth Publishing Co., 1982-1986 (Box 498)
  - Young Worker Publisher: Young Workers League, 1967-1968 (Box 499)
  - Young Worker Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Young Workers Liberation League, 1970-1983 (Box 499)
  - Young Worker: Official Organ of the Young Workers League Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Organization Committee for the Young Workers League of America, 1929-1930 (Box 499)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7697)
  - Your Military Left Place of publication: San Antonio, Tex. Publisher: G.I. Anti-war, 1972 (Box 165)
  - Youth Action for Socialism: Organ of the National Provisional Committee for a Socialist Youth League Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Provisional Committee for a Socialist Youth League, 1945 (Box 499)
  - Youth Bulletin Place of publication: Dublin, Ireland Publisher: Irish Young Socialists, 1972 (Box 436)
  - Youth Rising Place of publication: Ann Arbor, Mich. Publisher: Youth Liberation Front, 1972 (Box 281)